<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS的ABC on 抽筋儿的话语权</title>
    <link>//chouj.github.io/tags/rss%E7%9A%84abc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in RSS的ABC on 抽筋儿的话语权</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 13:34:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//chouj.github.io/tags/rss%E7%9A%84abc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[翻译]有关RSS的ABC</title>
      <link>//chouj.github.io/524/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 13:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chouj.github.io/524/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://pic.yupoo.com/xcchris/152046216d4e/07vxiyl1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;[翻译]有关RSS的ABC&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;[原文]&lt;a title=&#34;ABCs of RSS feeds&#34; href=&#34;http://www.feedforall.com/abcs-of-rss.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ABC&amp;#8217;s of RSS Feeds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[作者]Sharon Housley&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[翻译]抽筋儿&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[译者按]能力有限，欢迎指正。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[全文]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Implementing RSS (Really Simple Syndication) can be aided by an understanding of the terms relating to RSS. Learn the ABCs of RSS&amp;#8230;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;来学RSS的ABC吧，了解了这些和RSS有关的东东，你就能搞懂RSS啦。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A &amp;#8211; AutoDiscovery（自动识别）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Auto Discovery is code that is inserted into the header of an HTML web page, which then indicates to readers that an RSS feed is available for the content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果网页HTML源码的头部中有了自动识别编码，那么阅读器就能知道该网页有RSS feed可读取。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B &amp;#8211; Blogs（博客）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blogs are web logs that are updated regularly, usually on a daily basis. Blogs generally contain information related to a specific topic. In some cases, blogs are used as daily diaries about people&amp;#8217;s personal lives, political views, or even as social commentaries. The truth of the matter is that blogs can be shaped into whatever the author wants them to be. While initially thought of as diaries or online journals, blogs have evolved into the latest fresh web content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;每日更新或规律更新的网络日志就是博客，它往往有其特定的主题，比方个人日记，政治倾向，甚至是时事探讨。最关键的是，博主能依照他们的意愿决定博客的一切（译者注：请参照贵国基本国情理解），因此本被理解为线上日记的博客变成了网络上的新鲜内容发源地。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C &amp;#8211; Cache（缓存）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cache is a temporary storage area for frequently-accessed or recently-accessed data. Having certain data stored in a cache area speeds up the operation of the computer. Using a cache with RSS feeds will help minimize bandwidth and display an RSS feed&amp;#8217;s content quicker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;最近或经常调用的数据就会被堆放在缓存里。电脑就是有益于缓存而使得运行速度提高。在RSS feeds里配备缓存可以减少带宽占用并加快内容展示的速度。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>